<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Yufan Zhang</title>
    <link>http://yufanz.xyz/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Yufan Zhang</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://yufanz.xyz/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>MF-Net: A Novel Stylized Multilingual Font Generation Method</title>
      <link>http://yufanz.xyz/project/mfnet/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yufanz.xyz/project/mfnet/</guid>
      <description>Develop a GAN-based model to achieve fast few-shot font style transfer between unseen languages</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visualizing NFT Ethics: A Case Study on CryptoPunks</title>
      <link>http://yufanz.xyz/project/nftvis/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yufanz.xyz/project/nftvis/</guid>
      <description>Investigate CryptoPunks, the most famous collection in the NFT market, to explore and visualize its potential ethical issues.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using AlphaFold and GNN to Predict Catalytic Efficiency</title>
      <link>http://yufanz.xyz/project/alphafold/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yufanz.xyz/project/alphafold/</guid>
      <description>Utilize the output of AlphaFold as the enzyme feature to predict catalytic efficiency with GNN</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NFT Marketplace: How to Choose the Right NFT Marketplace for Artists and Collectors</title>
      <link>http://yufanz.xyz/project/nftartist/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yufanz.xyz/project/nftartist/</guid>
      <description>Authors: Yufan Zhang, Zichao Chen
SciEcon NFT Research Lab, SciEcon CIC
Medium
Introduction In the article NFT Marketplace: Introduction to NFT and NFT Marketplace’s Mechanism, we have given you the primary mechanism of NFT and the specialized NFT marketplaces. NFTs (Non-Fungible Tokens), records on a blockchain that represents pieces of digital media, have become extremely popular this year. NFT marketplaces around the world play a vital role in the trading and liquidity of NFTs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>按下快门：我的前10000张糟糕的摄影</title>
      <link>http://yufanz.xyz/blog/10000photos/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yufanz.xyz/blog/10000photos/</guid>
      <description>从很小的时候，我就被「摄影」所吸引，常常被各类杂志、博客和社交媒体上的摄影作品所折服。但在上大学之前，我都未曾拥有过一台真正意义上的相机，更多的时间是用我的iPhone进行拍摄。2020疫情刚爆发时，被困在学校的我为了一个Media&amp;amp;Arts课程的期末作业，购置了一台Sony A6100，开始习惯于通过按下快门记录生活。
在我眼里，「摄影」迷人的地方在于，有时候生活中的某个稍瞬即逝的场景，或会击中我的某处美学神经，又或是勾起我对于世界的感动，于是拿出相机把它拍下来。接着，对于照片的进一步加工，其实就是把打动我的部分放大，加强，把心中的美给实体化在一幅幅照片的过程。通过照片，别人才有了与我共同欣赏美景时的感动与共鸣。
法国人文摄影家Henri Cartier-Bresson说过这样一句话,
Your first 10000 photographs are your worst. 你的前 10000 张照片是你最糟糕的。
我写下这篇简短的Blog作为一个简陋的电子摄影集，来记录拿起相机的两年内用快门记录的瞬间。如果幸运的话，但愿这些照片是我最糟糕的照片。
让我们开始吧。
Blue: Sky and Sea 天蓝与海蓝 Weihai, China
Jul 2020
SONY A6100 | 50mm F2 1/640
Coffee or Orange 咖啡还是橘色 Shanghai, China
Oct 2021
SONY A6100 | 31mm F4 1/320
Busy Thriving 忙于成长 Kunshan, China
Nov 2021
SONY A6100 | 240mm F8 1/1000
Sunset Glow 晚霞 Jinan, China
Jun 2020
SONY A6100 | 50mm F1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating Higher Education Using Machine Learning</title>
      <link>http://yufanz.xyz/project/higheredu/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yufanz.xyz/project/higheredu/</guid>
      <description>Authors: Qinwanxian Liu, Chenyu Wang, Yufan Zhang
Meritotious Winner for MCM/ICM 2022
PDF | Certificate
Abstract Higher education is a core component of a sustainable society. It has gained significant momentum worldwide over the last three decades. To fairly evaluate the quality and sustainability of the existing higher education system in different countries, we constructed a Back-Propagation neuro network model. We assess seven representative countries.
In the first part, we carefully selected indices including enrollment ratio, Gender Parity Index, the number of Nobel prizes in different countries.</description>
    </item>
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
