<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on YufanZ</title>
    <link>http://yufanz.xyz/project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on YufanZ</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://yufanz.xyz/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Blockchain Network Analysis: A Comparative Studies of Decentralized Banks</title>
      <link>http://yufanz.xyz/project/bna/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yufanz.xyz/project/bna/</guid>
      <description>Authors: Yufan Zhang, Zichao Chen, Yutong Sun, Yulin Liu, Luyao Zhang
Paper accepted by SAI Computing Conference
GitHub
Abstract Decentralized finance (DeFi) is known for its unique mechanism design, which applies smart contracts to facilitate peer-to-peer transactions. The decentralized bank is a typical application of DeFi. Ideally, a decentralized bank should be decentralized in the transaction. However, many recent studies have found that decentralized bank has not achieved a significant degree of decentralization.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MF-Net: A Novel Stylized Multilingual Font Generation Method</title>
      <link>http://yufanz.xyz/project/mfnet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yufanz.xyz/project/mfnet/</guid>
      <description>Authors: Yufan Zhang, Junkai Man, Peng Sun
Paper presented at ACM Multimedia 2022
DOI: 10.1145/3503161.3548414
GitHub | MFont.net (coming soon in next year)
Introduction Designing fonts is never a easy task, especially for non-Latin languages such as Chinese for its complex glyph structures and large number of letters. Moreover, in real-world problems, designing a multilingual font is a even more challenging task that requires years of study, proficiency in the use of many professional tools and collaboration between multiple font designer for different languages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visualizing NFT Ethics: A Case Study on CryptoPunks</title>
      <link>http://yufanz.xyz/project/nftvis/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yufanz.xyz/project/nftvis/</guid>
      <description>Authors: Yufan Zhang, Zichao Chen, Luyao Zhang, Xin Tong
Accepted by ChinaVis 2022
arXiv | GitHub
Paper Abtract As a blockchain-based application, Non-Fungible Token (NFT) has received worldwide attention over the past few years. Digital artwork is the main form of NFT that can be stored on different blockchains. Although the NFT market is rapidly developing, we observed potential ethical and racial fairness issues in the design of NFT artworks due to a lack of ethical guidelines or censorship.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using AlphaFold and GNN to Predict Catalytic Efficiency</title>
      <link>http://yufanz.xyz/project/alphafold/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yufanz.xyz/project/alphafold/</guid>
      <description>Supervisors: Dr. Gaoyang Li, Prof. Huansheng Cao
Yufan Zhang, Yiyang Sun, Yang Yu, Jinxuan Zhang, Zixu Geng
GitHub
Project Introduction This project is part of the research initiative by Dr. Gaoyang Li and Prof. Huansheng Cao. The project aims to use AlphaFold and GNN to predict the catalytic efficiency of several species (e.g., Bacillus subtilis). The project is divided into two parts: the first part is to use AlphaFold to output the structural representation of the enzymes in the species, and the second part is to use GNN to harvest the previous AlphaFold output to predict the catalytic efficiency of all the catalytic processes in the species.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
