<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Yufan Zhang</title>
    <link>http://yufanz.xyz/project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Yufan Zhang</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://yufanz.xyz/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>MF-Net: A Novel Stylized Multilingual Font Generation Method</title>
      <link>http://yufanz.xyz/project/mfnet/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yufanz.xyz/project/mfnet/</guid>
      <description>Develop a GAN-based model to achieve fast few-shot font style transfer between unseen languages</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visualizing NFT Ethics: A Case Study on CryptoPunks</title>
      <link>http://yufanz.xyz/project/nftvis/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yufanz.xyz/project/nftvis/</guid>
      <description>Investigate CryptoPunks, the most famous collection in the NFT market, to explore and visualize its potential ethical issues.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using AlphaFold and GNN to Predict Catalytic Efficiency</title>
      <link>http://yufanz.xyz/project/alphafold/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yufanz.xyz/project/alphafold/</guid>
      <description>Utilize the output of AlphaFold as the enzyme feature to predict catalytic efficiency with GNN</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NFT Marketplace: How to Choose the Right NFT Marketplace for Artists and Collectors</title>
      <link>http://yufanz.xyz/project/nftartist/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yufanz.xyz/project/nftartist/</guid>
      <description>Authors: Yufan Zhang, Zichao Chen
SciEcon NFT Research Lab, SciEcon CIC
Medium
Introduction In the article NFT Marketplace: Introduction to NFT and NFT Marketplace’s Mechanism, we have given you the primary mechanism of NFT and the specialized NFT marketplaces. NFTs (Non-Fungible Tokens), records on a blockchain that represents pieces of digital media, have become extremely popular this year. NFT marketplaces around the world play a vital role in the trading and liquidity of NFTs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating Higher Education Using Machine Learning</title>
      <link>http://yufanz.xyz/project/higheredu/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yufanz.xyz/project/higheredu/</guid>
      <description>Authors: Qinwanxian Liu, Chenyu Wang, Yufan Zhang
Meritotious Winner for MCM/ICM 2022
PDF | Certificate
Abstract Higher education is a core component of a sustainable society. It has gained significant momentum worldwide over the last three decades. To fairly evaluate the quality and sustainability of the existing higher education system in different countries, we constructed a Back-Propagation neuro network model. We assess seven representative countries.
In the first part, we carefully selected indices including enrollment ratio, Gender Parity Index, the number of Nobel prizes in different countries.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
