<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on YufanZ</title>
    <link>http://example.org/project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on YufanZ</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Blockchain Network Analysis: A Comparative Studies of Decentralized Banks</title>
      <link>http://example.org/project/bns/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/project/bns/</guid>
      <description>Authors: Zichao Chen, Yulin Liu, Yufan Zhang, Luyao Zhang
GitHub</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MF-Net: A Novel Stylized Multilingual Font Generation Method</title>
      <link>http://example.org/project/mfnet/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/project/mfnet/</guid>
      <description>Authors: Yufan Zhang, Junkai Man, Peng Sun
Accepted by ACM Multimedia 2022
GitHub
Abstract Creating a complete stylized font library that helps the audience to perceive information from the text often requires years of study and proficiency in the use of many professional tools. Accordingly, automatic stylized font generation in a deep learning-based fashion is a desirable but challenging task that has attracted a lot of attention in recent years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visualizing NFT Ethics: A Case Study on CryptoPunks</title>
      <link>http://example.org/project/nftvis/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/project/nftvis/</guid>
      <description>Investigate CryptoPunks, the most famous collection in the NFT market, to explore and visualize its potential ethical issues.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using AlphaFold and GNN to Predict Catalytic Efficiency</title>
      <link>http://example.org/project/alphafold/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/project/alphafold/</guid>
      <description> Supervisors: Dr. Gaoyang Li, Prof. Huansheng Cao
Yufan Zhang, Yiyang Sun, Yang Yu, Jinxuan Zhang, Zixu Geng
GitHub
Using AlphaFold and GNN to Predict Catalytic Efficiency of Enzymes
Network Scratch </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
