<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>machine learning on Yufan Zhang</title>
    <link>/tags/machine-learning/</link>
    <description>Recent content in machine learning on Yufan Zhang</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/machine-learning/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>miniTorch</title>
      <link>/projects/minitorch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/minitorch/</guid>
      <description>GitHub Repo: iamyufan/minitorch</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MFont.net</title>
      <link>/projects/mfnet/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/mfnet/</guid>
      <description>MF-Net: A Novel Few-shot Stylized Multilingual Font Generation Method
GitHub Repo: iamyufan/MF-Net
Paper presented at the 30th ACM International Conference on Multimedia (MM ‘22) Authors: Yufan Zhang, Junkai Man, Peng Sun*
Introduction Designing fonts is never a simple task, especially when it comes to non-Latin languages like Chinese, which have intricate glyph patterns and a high number of characters. Furthermore, in the real world, creating a multilingual font poses an even greater challenge, requiring years of research, expertise in using numerous professional tools, and collaboration among multiple font designers specializing in various languages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blockchain Network Analysis</title>
      <link>/projects/bns/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/bns/</guid>
      <description>Paper presented at SAI Computing Conference 2023
Authors: Yufan Zhang, Zichao Chen, Yutong Sun, Yulin Liu*, and Luyao Zhang*
Introduction Decentralized finance (DeFi) is known for its unique mechanism design, which applies smart contracts to facilitate peer-to-peer transactions. The decentralized bank is a typical DeFi application. Ideally, a decentralized bank should be decentralized in the transaction. However, many recent studies have found that decentralized banks have not achieved a significant degree of decentralization.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
